- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
- Birthday Party -
Hey, Sooha!
Welcome.
We've been waiting for you!
What a lovely place.
Thanks for coming.
I bet it was tough getting out here
to the middle of the woods.
Shion's claiming he built the place.
I mean, it's not a total lie.
We bought this place with the money
we spent a long time saving.
True.
Sooha.
It's them.
Khan!
H-Hey.
Good to see you again.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sure the others will be glad, too.
What? Not really.
We only invited you to be polite, but you
actually came. Can't you read the room?
So typical of you guys.
Yeah, we're here because we knew
you'd be happy if we didn't show.
It was on purpose.
C-Come on. Let's go inside.
Wow!
This is my first time being
invited to a birthday party.
Really?
In fact, I've never even invited
friends to celebrate my own birthday.
So I was looking forward to
celebrating with a large group.
We have games, too.
Let's have tons of fun.
Yeah!
Just so you know,
we still don't trust you guys.
We don't trust you, either.
Right?
Really?
Is that true?
Happy birthday, everyone!
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Thanks, guys.
Yeah. Let's have fun today.
Tons of fun.
Hey, uh...
About that message...
Oh, that? Thanks.
What? You've been texting Sooha?
Yikes.
Who said you could do that?
So, what'd you guys talk about?
This.
A wolf cub?
You sent her a photo?
Are you trying to get her
attention with cute pictures?
You're so awkward.
See? Isn't it cute?
You're right! It is cute!
Send that to me, too.
What?!
Apparently, Khan loves animals.
He also sent me this, and this, and this.
Wait, wait, wait.
He doesn't love animals. He is an ani—
They're mostly pictures of wolf cubs, huh?
Yeah, because I like wolves.
But cats are actually my favorite.
Khan? Is something wrong?
I-It's nothing.
Oh, right!
Here.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Can we open it?
Of course.
They're anti-vampire items.
It's been so dangerous lately.
I just want you guys to be careful.
Th-Thanks. We'll treasure them.
Wow, you've got great taste.
You're trying to protect
them from vampire attacks?
You're so nice, Sooha.
You guys better have
brought something, too.
Of course we did.
Yeah.
Happy birthday.
That's...
We've got great taste, too.
Our gifts are similar, but you can
never have too many anti-vampire items.
These silver balls were expensive.
Here, catch.
Thanks. We'll treasure them.
This is great! You should be safe
with this many anti-vampire items.
Y-Yeah. Thanks a lot.
That's not much of a reaction.
Can't you be happier?
Yeah. Wait, don't tell me
you didn't like your gifts!
We're thrilled with them.
We were just wanting something like this.
Good thing you chose this, Tahel.
Right?
Oh, really? You picked this out?
We'll have to return the favor.
Hey, um...
Don't worry about it.
Here.
Yeah, your shocked expressions
were more than enough.
For me? Thank you.
We were just a little surprised.
But why?
We won't let it end like this.
Uh, no reason. Open it.
Should we go buy something now?
What is this? It's so cute!
It's a wolf cub!
Thank you. This is the
cutest photo I've seen.
Really? I'm glad you like it.
It's so cute.
Are you having fun?
What do you want?
I'm just saying hello.
I heard your leader ran into Sooha
on the night of the total eclipse.
Yeah.
Is it okay for a werewolf to
fall in love with a human girl?
Are you really one to talk?
Let me make one thing clear.
I'm not like you guys.
What's so funny?
It's ironic.
That night...
you transformed like us.
Meanwhile, there are others
who wish they could but can't.
Well, should we play a game?
Let's start with... Werewolf!
Werewolf?
It's a game where you guess who's lying.
Really? That sounds fun.
It's perfect for this party, you know?
Let's play.
I'll be the game master.
Game Master: Noa
You reside in a village where
people live happy lives.
However, werewolves disguised
as humans have arrived,
and they've begun attacking
villagers every night.
You must identify the evil werewolves
who are deceiving the villagers.
Please close your eyes.
Werewolves, open your eyes.
Werewolf: Najak
Werewolf: Tahel
Ugh, you?
Werewolf: Jaan
Shut up! They'll know it's us!
Morning has arrived.
Everyone, please open your eyes.
Villager: Enzy
Traitor: Khan
Knight: Heli
Seer: Sooha
Villager: Solon
Villager: Shion
Villager: Jino
Werewolf: Jaan
Medium: Jakah
Now, who are the werewolves?
Discuss amongst yourselves.
It's clearly one of you guys.
Huh?
Yeah.
Wait. You can't assume that yet.
Sooha, who do you think
are the werewolves?
Who, me? Well, I think
we'll find out at night.
Sooha, you're the seer, right?
Yeah.
By the way, I'm the knight.
No, you're not!
Are you stupid?
Huh?
Oh, um... that's because...
I'm actually the knight. Yeah! That's me!
Oh, really? Then you'd better protect me.
O-Of course I will.
I'm excited for tonight.
Y-Yeah...
Okay, time's up.
Everyone, who do you think
are the werewolves?
Point to vote.
Ready, and...
How'd you know?!
How could we not?
Your eyes have been darting around.
And you've been flustered this whole time.
Why'd you guys point at me, too?
Because you put us in danger—
Traitors!
Oh, that's me.
Idiot.
All right. Let's have cake.
Did you enjoy the party?
Yeah. I'm glad you invited me.
I've never had this much fun before.
I'm glad.
We'll have to celebrate
your birthday next.
Really? I'd love that!
But this time, I'll host
and invite you, Heli.
Huh?
I've never hosted a party before, though.
Okay. I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah!
Thanks for today.
Sure. Be careful.
You're not leaving yet?
No, we have to clean up.
We're staying here tonight.
Want some help?
We'll be fine.
Be careful on your way back.
Sooha!
Let's go back together.
Well, see you at school.
Thanks for waiting.
The food was pretty good, huh?
That was fun.
Yeah.
Would it be okay if I texted you more?
Of course. I'll look for
things to send you, too.
I forgot the present Khan gave me!
Sorry, I forgot something!
I'll go with—
No, that's okay.
See you later.
But the sun will set soon.
I can't believe I forgot Khan's gift.
I'd better hurry before it gets dark.
Huh?
Where did I put it?
There it is.
Maybe I'll help them after all.
But where did they go?
So this is where—
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
Sooha!
Please! Hear us out!
Don't talk to me, creep!
Heli.
I'm going after Sooha.
What for?
What are you going to say?
There's nothing you can say to her now.
She saw us like this.
But Heli...
What should we do now?
There's nothing we can do.
Rumors about us will spread
throughout the academy.
Then we'll have to run away.
Would Sooha...
Would Sooha tell everyone?
Doesn't she hate vampires
more than anything?
There's no way she'd leave us alone.
We should start by
talking to her in person.
Yeah! Heli, use telepathy
to contact her first.
When I contacted her earlier,
she refused to listen.
She called me a creep.
Jakah, find her.
Got it.
Sooha's energy is strong,
so it shouldn't take long to...
A horde of vampires!
Wh-What's going on?
Is Heli actually a vampire?
Not just Heli.
All of them.
Is that why they have those powers?
You're the ones who killed
our student, aren't you?
Is that why...
Could you bite my neck?
Oh, uh...
Is that why...
I-I'm not a vampire.
Please, believe me...
I do.
Is that why he said
he believed me?! But...
I thought I'd finally made a friend
who believed me since losing Chris.
I met friends who bore secrets like mine.
I thought school was
fun for the first time.
But it was all a lie.
Heli? Did you chase after me?
S-Stay back! There's nothing
I hate more than...
S-Someone help...
Help me, Khan!
Sooha?
Sooha, are you all right?!
I understand why you're shocked.
But we're different from
the vampires you hate.
Please, hear us out.
Does that mean...
Does that mean you're not a vampire?
And the others?
Please tell me it's not true.
That it's all a misunderstanding.
When we first met, you said you
believed that I wasn't a vampire.
It's because you knew I wasn't one of you!
That's why you could say that!
No! It's not like that!
Then why did you believe me so easily?
Khan?
Ch-Chris...
Are you crying, Sooha?
Huh? Oh, um...
Are you okay?
I don't know what happened,
but don't worry.
I'm here for you.
Chris...
You're my dear friend, Sooha.
Sooha, let's be friends.
Okay.
I'm sorry I couldn't come
see you right away.
I was afraid you wouldn't believe
that I'd come back to life.
I mean, it's unbelievable, right?
But I want you to believe me, Sooha.
I believe you.
Just like you believed me.
Heli!
You're with Sooha, right?
Jakah? What's going on?
Actually, we're—
Damn it! What's going on?
Why are there so many vampires?
Heli, I'm sensing an energy as
powerful as Sooha's next to her.
I really missed you.
I've spent years looking for you.
What is this?
Sooha.
You'll be my princess forever.
Get away from Sooha!
You should stay out of
this for your own sake.
Heli...
Chris...
Next time, Episode 7:
"Blue Moon: That's Fate."
- That's Fate -